Lewis W. Douglas papers, 1859-1974 (bulk 1880-1960)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series IV: Lewis W. Douglas Papers, 1906-1974
  - Subseries VII: Politics and World Affairs, 1960-1974
    - Correspondence (U.S.), Williams, Jack. 1964-1972 (Box 332, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence (U.S.), Wolman, Leo and family. 1960-1972 (Box 332, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence (Foreign), Agar, Herbert. 1964-1973 (Box 333, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (Foreign), Aitken, Max (Lord Beaverbrook). 1963-1964 (Box 333, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (Foreign), Berry, Michael and Pamela (Lord and Lady Hartwell). 1960-1974 (Box 333, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (Foreign), Butler, Richard A. 1963-1967 (Box 333, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (Foreign), Caccia, Harold. 1970-1973 (Box 333, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (Foreign), Churchill, Randolph and son. 1964-1967 (Box 333, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (Foreign), Churchill, Winston and Clementine. 1960-1974 (Box 333, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (Foreign), death of Winston Churchill. January-February 1965 (Box 333, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (Foreign), Cromer, Rowley. 1965-1971 (Box 333, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence (Foreign), Crowther, Geoffrey. 1960-1972 (Box 333, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence (Foreign), Dean, Patrick. 1962-1969 (Box 333, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence (Foreign), Douglas-Home, Alec. 1962-1973 (Box 333, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence (Foreign), Duncan, James S. 1961-1969 (Box 333, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence (Foreign), Eden, Anthony (Earl of Avon) and Clarissa. 1961-1973 (Box 333, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence (Foreign), Gascoyne-Cecil, Robert Arthur James (Lord Salisbury). 1962-1972 (Box 333, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence (Foreign), Glendevon, John. 1967-1972 (Box 333, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence (Foreign), Heath, Edward. 1965-1974 (Box 333, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence (Foreign), Ismay, Hastings Lionel. 1960-1969 (Box 333, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence (Foreign), Lloyd, Selwyn. 1961-1973 (Box 333, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence (Foreign), Macmillan, Harold. 1961-1974 (Box 333, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence (Foreign), Menzies, Robert. 1960-1968 (Box 333, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence (Foreign), Moore, Garrett (Earl of Drogheda). 1960-1973 (Box 333, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence (Foreign), Ormsby-Gore, David (Lord Harlech). 1962-1967 (Box 333, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence (Foreign), Pearson, Lester B. 1962-1973 (Box 333, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence (Foreign), Royal Family (England). 1960-1973 (Box 334, Folder 1-2)
    - Correspondence (Foreign), Salter, Arthur. 1961-1971 (Box 334, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (Foreign), Swinton, Philip and "Mollie." 1960-1974 (Box 334, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (Foreign), trevelyan, Humphrey. 1972-1973 (Box 334, Folder 5)
    - Lyndon B. Johnson, correspondence. 1960-1973 (Box 335, Folder 1-2)
    - Lyndon B. Johnson, LWD's statement about President Johnson. August 1964 (Box 335, Folder 3)
    - Lyndon B. Johnson, Johnson-Humphrey campaign. 1964 (Box 335, Folder 4)
    - Lyndon B. Johnson, National Independent Committee for President Johnson and Senator Humphrey. 1964 (Box 335, Folder 5)
    - Lyndon B. Johnson, Democratic National Committee. 1964-1974 (Box 335, Folder 6-7)
    - Atlantic Council, correspondence. 1961-1973 (Box 336, Folder 1-10)
    - Atlantic Instititute, correspondence. 1960-1964, 1970 (Box 337, Folder 1-3)
    - Atlantic Institute, report. 1963 (Box 337, Folder 4)
    - Business Committee for Tax Reduction. 1963-1964 (Box 337, Folder 5)
    - Center for the study of the President. 1973-1974 (Box 337, Folder 6)
    - Committee for Government of the People. 1966 (Box 337, Folder 7)
    - Committee to Strengthen the Frontiers of Freedom. 1959-1961 (Box 337, Folder 8)
    - Declaration of Atlantic Unity. 1960-1971 (Box 337, Folder 9-10)
    - International Movement for Atlantic Union. 1962-1973 (Box 337, Folder 11)
    - National Committee for International Development. 1965-1966 (Box 338, Folder 1)
    - National committee for Immigration Reform. 1965 (Box 338, Folder 2)
    - National Council on Crime and Delinquency. 1967-1974 (Box 338, Folder 3-5)
    - President's Task Force on American Indians, correspondence. 1966-1968 (Box 338, Folder 6-8)
    - President's Task Force on American Indians, miscellaneous reports. no date (Box 338, Folder 9)
    - Washinton Institute for Foreign Affairs. 1962-1964 (Box 338, Folder 10)
    - Balance of Payments. 1965-1966 (Box 339, Folder 1)
    - Bank Holding Company Act. 1966, 1970 (Box 339, Folder 2)
    - Tax Reform Bill (H.R. 13270), correspondence. 1969 (Box 339, Folder 3-4)
    - Tax Reform Bill (H.R. 13270), publications. 1969 (Box 339, Folder 5)
    - Trade Bill, 10% surcharge on imports. 1970-1971 (Box 339, Folder 6-7)
    - Capital Gains Tax. 1970-1973 (Box 339, Folder 8)
    - Gold, the Dollar, Economics, correspondence. 1960-1971 (Box 339, Folder 9)
    - Gold, the Dollar, Economics, publications. 1960-1972 (Box 339, Folder 10)
    - Walter Stewart Testimony before the Macmillan Committee. 1930 (Box 339, Folder 11)
    - Martin, William McC. (Federal Reserve System). 1960-1970 (Box 340, Folder 1-2)
    - Burns, Arthur F. 1968-1973 (Box 340, Folder 3-4)
    - Port Authority of New York. 1960-1962 (Box 341, Folder 1)
    - Wilderness Bill. 1961 (Box 341, Folder 2)
    - Mexican Duck Treaty. 1962 (Box 341, Folder 3)
    - Labor Issues. 1962, 1972 (Box 341, Folder 4)
    - Limited Test Ban Treaty. 1963 (Box 341, Folder 5)
    - Oil Shale (correspondence with Joe T. Juhan). 1967 (Box 341, Folder 6-7)
    - Vietnam, correspondence. 1965-1970 (Box 341, Folder 8)
    - Vietnam, LWD's letter to Ellsworth Bunker, via President Johnson. October 31, 1967 (Box 341, Folder 9)
    - Vietnam, business executives move for Vietnam Peace. 1967-1969 (Box 341, Folder 10)
    - Vietnam, clippings, publications, miscellaneous material. no date (Box 341, Folder 11)
    - Watergate. 1973-1974 (Box 341, Folder 12)
    - Central Arizona Project (CAP), Fannin, Paul. 1963-1969 (Box 342, Folder 1)
    - Central Arizona Project (CAP), Goldwater, Barry. 1963 (Box 342, Folder 2)
    - Central Arizona Project (CAP), Hayden, Carl. 1964-1968 (Box 342, Folder 3)
    - Central Arizona Project (CAP), Rhodes, John J. 1964-1968 (Box 342, Folder 4)
    - Central Arizona Project (CAP), Williams, Jack. 1967 (Box 342, Folder 5)
    - Central Arizona Project (CAP), miscellaneous and general correspondence. 1962-1973 (Box 342, Folder 6-12)
    - Central Arizona Project (CAP), Udall, Morris K. 1965-1969 (Box 343, Folder 1-3)
    - Central Arizona Project (CAP), Udall, Stewart L. 1964-1969 (Box 343, Folder 4)
    - Central Arizona Project (CAP), Monzoni, John. 1966-1968 (Box 343, Folder 5)
    - Central Arizona Project (CAP), Matthiessen, Erard A. 1968-1969 (Box 343, Folder 6)
    - Central Arizona Project (CAP), Smith, Hugh R.H. 1967-1968 (Box 343, Folder 7-12)
    - Central Arizona Project (CAP), Arizona Power Authority. 1963-1971 (Box 344, Folder 1-7)
    - Central Arizona Project (CAP), Quinton, Harold (Southern California Edison). 1963-1968 (Box 344, Folder 8)
    - Central Arizona Project (CAP), maps. no date (Box 345, Folder 1)
    - Central Arizona Project (CAP), miscellaneous material. no date (Box 345, Folder 2)
    - Central Arizona Project (CAP), Wilbur Ray L. Hoover Dam Power and Water Contracts and Related Data. U.S. Government Print Office. 1933 (Box 345)
    - Central Arizona Project (CAP), In the Supreme Court of the United States, October Term, State of Arizona, complainant v. State of California. 1960 (Box 345)
    - Central Arizona Project (CAP), U.S. Department of the Interior, Pacific Southwest Plan. August 1963 (Box 345)
    - Central Arizona Project (CAP), U.S. Congress, House, Committee on Interior & Insular Affairs: Colorado River Basin Project. Hearings on H.R. 3300. March 13-17, 1967 (Box 345)
    - Central Arizona Project (CAP), Arizona Highways. January 1964 and May 1968 (Box 345)
    - Office material, LWD and secretarial staff. 1962-1974 (Box 346, Folder 1-2)
    - Office material, letters of condolences and sympathy (from LWD). 1960-1974 (Box 346, Folder 3-5)
    - Office material, letters of introduction and recommendation. 1960-1973 (Box 346, Folder 6-11)
    - Requests from students and writers involved in research regarding LWD's career. 1960-1974 (Box 347, Folder 1-3)
    - Requests for LWD's papers. no date (Box 347, Folder 4)
    - Requests for information and/or advice. no date (Box 347, Folder 5)
    - Requests for autographs and/or photographs. no date (Box 347, Folder 6)
    - Requests for opinions. no date (Box 347, Folder 7)
    - Requests for financial assistance. no date (Box 347, Folder 8)
    - Requests to see LWD. no date (Box 347, Folder 9)
    - Requests, miscellaneous. no date (Box 347, Folder 10)
    - Invitations (declined), to speak. 1959-1972 (Box 348, Folder 1-2)
    - Invitations (declined), to serve on boards and committees. 1960-1974 (Box 348, Folder 3)
    - Invitations (declined), to participate in and/or attend conferences, seminars, lectures. 1960-1972 (Box 348, Folder 4)
    - Invitations (declined), to appear on radio or TV. 1963-1969 (Box 348, Folder 5)
    - Invitations (declined), to attend various ceremonies. 1960-1973 (Box 349, Folder 1-3)
    - Invitations (declined), various social events honoring specific individuals. 1960-1974 (Box 349, Folder 4-5)
    - Invitations (declined), miscellaneous social events. 1960-1973 (Box 349, Folder 6-7)
    - Invitations (declined), join or subscribe. 1960-1972 (Box 349, Folder 8)
    - Invitations (declined), appeals for funds. 1961-1974 (Box 349, Folder 9-10)
    - British Channel Tunnel, correspondence. 1960-1973 (Box 350, Folder 1-5)
    - British Channel Tunnel, A Study of Organisation for a Channel Tunnell Company. February 1964 (Box 350)
    - Visit of Princess Margaret and Lord Snowden to the U.S., plans and arrangements. November 1965 (Box 351, Folder 1)
    - Visit of Princess Margaret and Lord Snowden to the U.S., correspondence. November 1965 (Box 351, Folder 2)
    - Visit of Princess Margaret and Lord Snowden to the U.S., correspondence (Royal Family). 1964-1966 (Box 351, Folder 3)
    - Visit of Princess Margaret and Lord Snowden to the U.S., Offers and Requests by others to participate. November 1965 (Box 351, Folder 4)
    - Visit of Princess Margaret and Lord Snowden to the U.S., gifts. November 1965 (Box 351, Folder 5)
    - Visit of Princess Margaret and Lord Snowden to the U.S., clippings. November 1965 (Box 351, Folder 6)
    - Visit of Princess Margaret and Lord Snowden to the U.S., Financial correspondence and records. November 1965 (Box 351, Folder 7)
    - Visit of Princess Margaret and Lord Snowden to the U.S., LWD's party, Arizona Inn, Tucson, AZ. November 10, 1965 (Box 351, Folder 8)
    - Visit of Princess Margaret and Lord Snowden to the U.S., trip to Page, AZ and Lake Powell. November 12-13, 1965 (Box 351, Folder 9)
    - Visit of Princess Margaret and Lord Snowden to the U.S., White House Party, Washington, D.C. November 17, 1965 (Box 351, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence (miscellaneous), mining. 1960-1973 (Box 352, Folder 1-2)
    - Correspondence (miscellaneous), mining (Anaconda). 1966-1968 (Box 352, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (miscellaneous), mining (Anaconda and Santa Tomas Village). 1965-1966 (Box 352, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (miscellaneous), mining (Phelps Dodge). 1964-1974 (Box 352, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (miscellaneous), mining (George Bott). 1959-1973 (Box 352, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (miscellaneous), mining (Robert P. Koenig). 1962-1970 (Box 352, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (miscellaneous), Continental Copper and Steel Industries, Inc. 1966-1972 (Box 352, Folder 8-12)
    - Correspondence (miscellaneous), American Institute for Foregin Trade, Phoenix, AZ. 1969-1973 (Box 353, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (miscellaneous), Thunderbird Graduate School of International Management, Glendale, AZ. 1969-1973 (Box 353, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (miscellaneous), Anglo-American College, Aylescot, Oxfordshire, England. 1966-1971 (Box 353, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (miscellaneous), Arizona State University, Tempe, AZ. 1961-1972 (Box 353, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (miscellaneous), Deerfield Academy, Deerfield, MA. 1966-1970 (Box 353, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (miscellaneous), Institute of Modern Languages, Washington, D.C. 1966 (Box 353, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (miscellaneous), Prescott College, Prescott, AZ. 1962-1970 (Box 353, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (miscellaneous), Southern Arizona School for Boys, Tucson, AZ. 1968-1971 (Box 353, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (miscellaneous), Parker, Gordon Rae (South African Student) Scholarship appeal. 1964 (Box 353, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence (miscellaneous), education. 1968-1972 (Box 353, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence (miscellaneous), Africa. 1961-1974 (Box 354, Folder 1-3)
    - Correspondence (miscellaneous), Commodore Marr and the Last sailing from NY of the "Queen Elizabeth." 1968-1973 (Box 354, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (miscellaneous), International Industrial Conference, San Francisco, CA. September 11-15, 1961 (Box 354, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (miscellaneous), Tattoo of the Queen's Guards, madison Square Garden, NYC. October 1-13, 1968 (Box 354, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (miscellaneous), Order of the British Empire Service of Dedication, St. Paul's Cathedral, London. May 19, 1971 (Box 354, Folder 7)
    - Articles, miscellaneous. 1953-1965 (Box 355, Folder 1)
    - Articles, foreward to The Businessman's Guide to Britain. 1955 (Box 355, Folder 2)
    - Articles, introduction to John Osborne's book on Britain ( Life World Library). 1961 (Box 355, Folder 3)
    - Articles, "The Qualities of Leadership: Churchill as Diplomat," Atlantic. March 1965 (Box 355, Folder 4-5)
    - Articles, "The Colorado River," Arizona Highways. May 1968 (Box 355, Folder 6-7)
    - Articles, editorial on thermal power-plant for The American West. March 1970 (Box 355, Folder 8)
    - Articles, foreward to The Inner Circle, by Joan Astley. 1970 (Box 355, Folder 9)
    - Articles, "A Simple and Objective Analysis of the Smelter Smoke Problem." 1971 (Box 355, Folder 10)
    - Articles, "Sketch," about Grenville Clark for a book to be published by Dartmouth College. 1970-1973 (Box 355, Folder 11)
    - Articles, McGill University for a proposed book. 1971-1972 (Box 355, Folder 12)
    - Articles, James Douglas for The Golden Spike, published by the American Geographical Society. 1969 (Box 355, Folder 13)
    - Articles, "Memorandum" on Presidential Nominations. 1972-1973 (Box 355, Folder 14)
    - Articles, Clemenceau for The History Makers, edited by Sir John Wheeler-Bennett. 1972-1974 (Box 355, Folder 15)
    - Articles, proposals for books or articles by LWD. 1961-1966 (Box 355, Folder 16)
    - Speeches, various. 1960-1969 (Box 356, Folder 1)
    - Speeches, Europe House, London. June 29, 1960 (Box 356, Folder 2)
    - Speeches, New York University Hall of Fame for Great Americans (NYC). October 27, 1960 (Box 356, Folder 3)
    - Speeches, Arizona Bankers Convention (Tucson, AZ). November 11, 1960 (Box 356, Folder 4)
    - Speeches, American Institute for Foreign Trade Commencement (Phoenix, AZ). January 22, 1961 (Box 356, Folder 5)
    - Speeches, Tucson Rotary Club (Tucson, AZ). March 15, 1961 (Box 356, Folder 6)
    - Speeches, Humble Oil Service Station Manger's Convention (Phoenix, AZ). March 23, 1961 (Box 356, Folder 7)
    - Speeches, National Association of Secretaries of State Annual Conference (Tucson, AZ). October 13, 1961 (Box 356, Folder 8)
    - Speeches, YMCA Convention (Douglas, AZ). February 26, 1962 (Box 356, Folder 9)
    - Speeches, Association of Stock Exchange Firms Regional Meeting (Salt Lake City, UT). September 23, 1963 (Box 356, Folder 10)
    - Speeches, Arizona-Sonora Committee Conference (Hermosillo, Sonora, Mexico). January 30, 1964 (Box 356, Folder 11)
    - Speeches, Daughters of the British Empire of the U.S. Convention (NYC). May 26, 1965 (Box 356, Folder 12)
    - Speeches, American Mining Congress Convention (Las Vegas, NV). October 14, 1965 (Box 356, Folder 13)
    - Speeches, Phoenix Rotary Club (Phoenix, AZ). January 28, 1966 (Box 356, Folder 14)
    - Speeches, British-American Chamber of Commerce Luncheon for Princess Alexandra (NYC). October 3, 1967 (Box 356, Folder 15)
    - Speeches, Nucleus Club (Phoenix and Tucson, AZ). February 8-9, 1968 (Box 356, Folder 16)
    - Speeches, Arizona Chapter of the Bank Administration Insititute meeting (Tucson, AZ). January 15, 1969 (Box 356, Folder 17)
    - Speeches, Motorola Executive Institute commencement (Vail, AZ). October 3, 1969 (Box 356, Folder 18)
    - Speeches, GAC Corporation Meeting (Rio Rico Inn, AZ). January 28, 1971 (Box 356, Folder 19)
    - Speeches, St. Andrew's Society of the State of New York Anniversary Banquet (NYC). December 1, 1971 (Box 356, Folder 20)
    - Speeches, Radio and TV. 1959-1970 (Box 356, Folder 21)
    - Speeches, Radio and TV (BBC Projected Tribute to Winston Churchill). 1959-1960 (Box 356, Folder 22)
    - Arizona, Citizen's Committee on the Salt River Project Tax Question (correspondence, Governor Paul Fannin). March-April 1963 (Box 357, Folder 1)
    - Arizona, Citizen's Committee on the Salt River Project Tax Question (correspondence). March 5-22, 1963 (Box 357, Folder 2)
    - Arizona, Citizen's Committee on the Salt River Project Tax Question (statements to the committee). March 25, 1963 (Box 357, Folder 3)
    - Arizona, Citizen's Committee on the Salt River Project Tax Question (supplementary material to the committee). March 27, 1963 (Box 357, Folder 4)
    - Arizona, Citizen's Committee on the Salt River Project Tax Question (correspondence). March 27-September 1963 (Box 357, Folder 5)
    - Arizona, Citizen's Committee on the Salt River Project Tax Question (correspondence, Greig Scott). March-August 1963 (Box 357, Folder 6)
    - Arizona, Citizen's Committee on the Salt River Project Tax Question (correspondenc, Governor Jack Williams). February-May 1969 (Box 357, Folder 7)
    - Arizona, Citizen's Committee on the Salt River Project Tax Question (correspondence). 1964-1968, January-February 1969 (Box 357, Folder 8)
    - Arizona, Citizen's Committee on the Salt River Project Tax Question (material from Tucson Gas and Electric Co.). February 19, 1969 (Box 357, Folder 9)
    - Arizona, Citizen's Committee on the Salt River Project Tax Question (correspondence). March 3-7, 1969 (Box 357, Folder 10)
    - Arizona, Citizen's Committee on the Salt River Project Tax Question (replies from TGE and Arizona Public Service Co.) March 7, 1969 (Box 357, Folder 11)
    - Arizona, Citizen's Committee on the Salt River Project Tax Question (correspondence). March 11-31, 1969 (Box 357, Folder 12)
    - Arizona, Citizen's Committee on the Salt River Project Tax Question (correspondnce). April 1969 (Box 357, Folder 13)
    - Arizona, Citizen's Committee on the Salt River Project Tax Question (miscellaneous notes by LWD). no date (Box 358, Folder 1)
    - Arizona, Citizen's Committee on the Salt River Project Tax Question (versions of legislative bills). no date (Box 358, Folder 2)
    - Arizona, Citizen's Committee on the Salt River Project Tax Question (miscellaneous charts and tables). no date (Box 358, Folder 3)
    - Arizona, Citizen's Committee on the Salt River Project Tax Question ( Salt River Project). 1963 (Box 358)
    - Arizona, Citizen's Committee on the Salt River Project Tax Question (briefing book). no date (Box 359, Folder 1)
    - Arizona, Citizen's Committee on the Salt River Project Tax Question (Salt River Project Area Information). no date (Box 359, Folder 2)
    - Arizona, Citizen's Committee on the Salt River Project Tax Question (publications regarding issuance of bonds). no date (Box 359, Folder 3)
    - Arizona, Citizen's Committee on the Salt River Project Tax Question (audit by Arthur Anderson and Co.; U.S. Supreme Court Jurisdictional Statement). no date (Box 359, Folder 4)
    - Arizona, Citizen's Committee on the Salt River Project Tax Question (various brochures and publications about the project). no date (Box 359, Folder 5)
    - Arizona, Citizen's Committee on the Salt River Project Tax Question (miscellaneous background material). no date (Box 359, Folder 6)
    - Arizona, Citizen's Committee on the Salt River Project Tax Question ( Salt River Project). 1969 (Box 359)
    - Arizona, University of Arizona. 1960-1973 (Box 360, Folder 1-2)
    - Arizona, University of Arizona (Arizona Medical School study). 1960-1967 (Box 360, Folder 3)
    - Arizona, Tucson International Airport. 1960-1964 (Box 360, Folder 4)
    - Arizona, Tucson Newspapers. 1960-1973 (Box 360, Folder 5)
    - Arizona, Tucson Art Center Churchill Show. 1966-1967 (Box 360, Folder 6)
    - Arizona, Cable TV for Tucson. 1965-1967 (Box 360, Folder 7)
    - Arizona, Sugar Refinery in Arizona. 1963-1967 (Box 361, Folder 1)
    - Arizona, Nuclear Site in Arizona. 1965-1970 (Box 361, Folder 2)
    - Arizona, Arizona Advisory Council on Fiscal Policy. 1966 (Box 361, Folder 3)
    - Arizona, El Paso and Southwestern Railroad Engine no.1. 1966-1967 (Box 361, Folder 4)
    - Arizona, Air pollution and smelter smoke (correspondence). 1969-1972 (Box 361, Folder 5-9)
    - Arizona, Air pollution and smelter smoke (piblications). no date (Box 361, Folder 10)
    - Arizona, miscellaneous topics. no date (Box 361, Folder 11)
    - U.S. Advisory Commission on Information, correspondence. 1956-1973 (Box 362, Folder 1-6)
    - U.S. Advisory Commission on Information, report: United Kingdom. 1960 (Box 362, Folder 7)
    - U.S. Advisory Commission on Information, report: Britain, France, Germany, Belgium. 1961 (Box 362, Folder 8)
    - U.S. Advisory Commission on Information, report: South Africa. 1961 (Box 362, Folder 9)
    - Committees (miscellaneous), American Committee to Preserve Abu Simbel. 1965-1967 (Box 363, Folder 1)
    - Committees (miscellaneous), National United Nations Day Committee. 1966-1973 (Box 363, Folder 2)
    - Committees (miscellaneous), Save St. Paul's Cathedral (U.S. Committee). 1971-1973 (Box 363, Folder 3)
    - Committees (miscellaneous). 1953-1965 (Box 363, Folder 4)
    - Committees (miscellaneous), honorary committees. 1954-1973 (Box 363, Folder 5-7)
    - Committees (miscellaneous), honorary committees (Comite Pro-Monumento a Jesus Garcia). 1966 (Box 363, Folder 8)
    - Committees (miscellaneous), LWD as a sponsor. no date (Box 363, Folder 9)
  - Subseries VIII: Organizations
    - Arizona Organizations
      - Arizona Water Resources Committee, correspondence. 1956-1973 (Box 364, Folder 1-4)
      - American Red Cross (Central Arizona Chapter). 1925-1926 (Box 365, Folder 1)
      - Arizona Business Development Corporation. 1966 (Box 365, Folder 2-4)
      - Arizona Heritage Council. 1963-1967 (Box 365, Folder 5)
      - Arizona-Mexico West Coast Trade Commission. 1959-1967 (Box 365, Folder 6-7)
      - Arizona World Trade Association. 1965-1967 (Box 365, Folder 8)
      - Boys Scouts of America (Arizona Councils). 1929-1953 (Box 365, Folder 9)
      - Hospital Planning Council for Greater Tucson. 1964-1968 (Box 366, Folder 1-2)
      - Mining Club of the Southwest. 1971-1973 (Box 366, Folder 3)
      - Radio Free Europe Fund (Arizona State Committee). 1963 (Box 366, Folder 4)
      - St. Luke's Home/St. Luke's Hospital (Phoenix, AZ). 1926-1969 (Box 366, Folder 5)
      - Tucson Art Center. 1968-1973 (Box 366, Folder 6)
      - United Nations Association of the U.S. (Tucson Chapter). 1962-1972 (Box 366, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous Arizona Organizations. 1927-1972 (Box 366, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous Arizona Committees. 1955-1966 (Box 366, Folder 9)